Women Against War; Records apap391
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Yahoo Group Correspondence, 2002-2021
  - OWN Women Against War Action, 2001
    - No Money For War, why to oppose the Supplemental Spending Bill, a message from Code Pink, 2007 March 19
    - Re: WAWaction What an inspiring demonstration!, 2007 March 19
    - Fwd: [spam] Re: WAWaction What an inspiring demonstration!, 2007 March 19
    - Photo's of Sunday's Demonstration, 2007 March 19
    - The Times Union and The Troy Record 3-19-07 Peace Walk Coverage, 2007 March 19
    - Re: WAWaction The Times Union and The Troy Record 3-19-07 Peace Walk Coverage, 2007 March 19
    - Fwd: Re: WAWaction The Times Union and The Troy Record 3-19-07 Peace Walk Coverage, 2007 March 19
    - Fwd: [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] Margaret Mead Fival, Roots Ns & Limbs, Trio X, Open Source, 2007 March 20
    - Fwd: WB Happenings--Dinner & a Movie Rescheduled, 2007 March 20
    - Fwd: Call Now: It's Not Too Late to Stop $$ for War, 2007 March 21
    - Fwd: Continuing the Struggle to End Iraq War Funding, 2007 March 22
    - Remembering The Fallen, 2007 March 22
    - WAW March Meeting Notes from Lynn Otty, 2007 March 23
    - Event Reminder: International Peace Activist, Kathy Kelly at Bethlehem Town Hall, 445 Delaware Avenue, Delmar,Saturday, March 24, 2007 at 6:30 PM, 2007 March 23
    - A requ from Jim Fulmer for those intered in helping the families of Yassin Aref and Mohammed Musharref Hossain with time, skills or energy, 2007 March 23
    - McNulty explains his vote, 2007 March 24
    - nominations for women peacemakers, 2007 March 25
    - Week long Tibetan Peace Mandala creation and interfaith programs/ceremonies at College of St. Rose, March 26th through March 30th., 2007 March 25
    - FW: Filling in the Gaps in American History, 2007 March 26
    - WAW to co-sponsor Art Opening and Potluck with Woodstock Women In Black...at 6 PM/ Film at 7 PM followed by discussion, Wednesday, April 4th., 2007 March 26
    - Fwd: Photos from March 18th Peace Walk, 2007 March 26
    - Fwd: photos of march, 2007 March 26
    - [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] "China Blue"--Margaret Mead Film & Video Fival, 2007 March 26
    - Photos from Peace Walk. Great photos! But large files are problematical for some members, 2007 March 27
    - from CodePink: a way to thank House members for voting no on $100 billion for Iraq, 2007 March 27
    - Re: WAWaction from CodePink: a way to thank House members for voting no on $1..., 2007 March 28
    - Organizing Meeting for Art Exhibit, "Missing Peace" ...Thursday, April 12th, 6 PM at the Women's Building, 2007 March 28
    - Call for Art Submissions for the show "Missing Peace" at the Women's Building, 2007 March 28
    - Yahoo Goes Wacky!!!, 2007 March 28
    - Code Pink video, 2007 March 30
    - difficulty accessing Washington Post Code Pink video, 2007 March 30
    - Guantanamo screening, 2007 March 30
    - Women Against War to co-sponsor three April events at The Sanctuary For Independent Media, Wednesday 4/4, Monday, 4/16, Tuesday, 4/24, 2007 April 1
    - Reminder of Venezuela event, 2007 April 2
    - Cindy Sheehan is coming!, 2007 April 3
    - Fwd: [Fwd: Re: co-sponsorship of "The Ground Truth"], 2007 April 3
    - delivery to Sen. Clinton's office Wednesday, 2007 April 3
    - From the webmaster for Remembering the Fallen, March 18th, Report on the Meeting with Senator Clinton's Office and updates on the website, 2007 April 5
    - Change in WAW general meeting format....NO APRIL MEETING...May 17 focus on Iran, overview and discussion, 2007 April 5
    - Clinton disses the peace movement again, 2007 April 5
    - how to contact Remembering the Fallen re failed delivery of posters, etc. to Senator Clinton, 2007 April 6
    - Fwd: Fasting For Love of Peace, Support local activists facing court date, 2007 April 8
    - Grannies for Peace & Women Against War at Step It Up 2007, 2007 April 9
    - Invitation to film showing: The Ground Truth, 2007 April 9
    - Iraqi Government Representative to speak in Albany on Tuesday, 2007 April 9
    - "The Ground Truth" Saturday, April 14th, 2007 April 10
    - "The Ground Truth" Saturday, April 21st, 2007 April 10
    - Join us on Wed April 18th: Event linking Tax Day and Iraq War!, 2007 April 10
    - Please Join us on Wednesday, April 18th from 4PM to 6PM as we express our outrage to the FBI for their behavior in our Community, 2007 April 11
    - Update-Occupation Project, 2007 April 11
    - BE PRESENT--Women's Bldg this Monday, 2007 April 11
    - GNP presents "Who Killed Electric Car", 2007 April 11
    - Update on the Occupation Project, 2007 April 11
    - Speaker from FOR available for talks about Iran in Early May, in schools, places of worship, peace groups, 2007 April 11
    - [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] Trio Tarana on Sunday, Jeremy Scahill on Monday, 2007 April 12
    - "Out of Balance: ExxonMobil's Impact on Climate Change" film at Rotterdam Public Library, April 17th, 6:30 PM, 2007 April 12
    - talk on civilian deaths in Iraq, 2007 April 12
    - Persons of Inter: A flim about Civil Rights for profiled communities, April 18th, 6 PM dinner and a movie at Albahy Law School, 2007 April 13
    - [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] Trio Tarana cancelled...Jeremy Scahill still on for tomorrow night..., 2007 April 15
    - GRANNIES TO PROT NATIONWIDE ON TAX DAY (press release), 2007 April 16
    - [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] Jeremy Scahill CONFIRMED, 2007 April 16
    - Scott Ritter to speak on the Crisis in U.S -- Iran relations, Tuesday, April 24th at 7 PM, Potluck at 6 PM at The Sanctuary for Independent Media, 2007 April 16
    - A story of sisterhood, 2007 April 17
    - The story about sisterhood that Maud Easter sent to the list yerday (Tuesday, 4/17), 2007 April 18
    - Iran - good information for our WAW strategizing, 2007 April 19
    - Petition of possible inter about postal rate increases for small independent periodicals, 2007 April 19
    - [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] Annie Sprinkle, Scott Ritter, Jeff Cher, 2007 April 19
    - Please note: Laterstarting time for "The Ground Truth", Saturday April 21st, 2007 April 19
    - Organizing Meeting Invitation: Thursday 4/26, 5:30 PM to 7 PM for June 8th End the Occupation rally by The Palinian Rights Committee, 2007 April 21
    - Reminder: GNP presents "Who Killed The Electric Car?" Monday, April 23rd, 2007 April 22
    - The Kings Mall 7, 2007 April 22
    - Women Against War, "Vision Statement" that will guide our work, 2007 April 23
    - Fwd: Re: WAWaction Women Against War, "Vision Statement" that will guide our work, 2007 April 23
    - A thank you note and brief summary of the Scott Ritter talk at the Sanctuary for Independent Media... a video will be available, 2007 April 25
    - Lead researcher on 650,000 Iraq War deaths study speaking tonight!, 2007 April 26
    - March with Cindy Sheehan " Mother of a March" DC, 2007 April 26
    - Emergency Veto Response Rallies, Albany/Colonie & Saratoga A "Heads Up" about upcoming rallies after George Bush vetos the Iraq Accountability bill, 2007 April 27
    - Fwd: [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] Evidence, Sacco & Vanzetti, plus The African Film Fival, 2007 April 27
    - Fw: please read and consider signing on in support, 2007 April 29
    - Concerned Citizens for The Sake of World Peace, 2007 April 30
    - ALERT: Prot Bush's Veto of Iraq bill: WEDNESDAY May 2nd: Albany & Saratoga, 2007 May 1
    - Women of all Ages Please Join Us to Stand in Washington Park for Peace, Saturday May 12th from 1 PM to 2 PM, 2007 May 1
    - The TEN COMMANDMENTS of the People, 2007 May 3
    - Fwd: [The Sanctuary For Independent Media] Anne Feeney, 2007 May 3
    - People building Peace, send a letter to Iran with a woman traveling with FOR this month, 2007 May 3
    - People building Peace, letters to Iran....response from Cathy Callan, 2007 May 4
    - Women Against War special strategy meeting on Iran - Thursday May 17th!, 2007 May 8
    - Fwd: RE-MEDIA: correction- use this to post and send please, 2007 May 8
    - REMINDER about Stand in the Park for Peace, Saturday, May 12, 2007, 1 PM to 2 PM, Washington Park, Albany, 2007 May 9
    - May 14 Rally in Albany, 2007 May 10
    - Travel to Paline, 2007 May 10
    - The Sanctuary For Independent Media- InterACT Troy: this Saturday (May 12th)!, 2007 May 10
    - Michael Haas author of "George Bush, War Criminal?" at Albany Law, Tomorrow, Wednesday, 2/18 from 4:30 PM to 6 PM, 2009 February 17
    - Invitation to hear Connie Frisbee Houde speak on Afghanistan at Islamic Center; this Sun, Feb 22, 2009 February 17
    - Good action opportunity on Afghanistan: 17,000 troops, but where is the plan?, 2009 February 18
    - Fw: Amiri Baraka & Rob Brown: Somebody Blew Up America, Upstate Girls, 2009 February 19
    - Apartment Needs for 5 Iraqi Refugees, 2009 February 19
    - Report on Saturday's Grannies for Peace Valentine's Vigil, 2009 February 19
    - WAW links heath care & military spending at Citizen Action Sat media event, 2009 February 19
    - February 15th NEPAJAC meeting summary, with follow-up actions and contacts listed, 2009 February 20
    - The blog writers of WAGING PEACE are looking for a few good women writers to join our blogging team [and also more commenters, men or women], 2009 February 21
    - PLEASE SIGN PEACE GRANDMOTHERS PETITION TO OBAMA--OUT OF AFGHANISTAN--Don't send more troops, 2009 February 22
    - New Iran Bulletin, 2009 February 23
    - Two events about Paline and Israel scheduled for this coming weekend: Saturday, 2/28 from 1:30 PM to 3:30 PM, and Sunday, March 1st, 3 PM, 2009 February 23
    - 100 Days Campaign To Close Guantanamo and End Torture - UPDATE & GETTING INVOLVED (WAW has signed on to this set of actions), 2009 February 24
    - An action notice from Grace White "Take Action: President Obama to Sanction Israel?', 2009 February 25
    - Troy Goes Splatto (Splatto Fival Chorus) Saturday, 2/28, 8 PM in Troy, 2009 February 25
    - Opportunities for Volunteering and Peacemaking in the Middle East, 2009 February 27
    - Flier About Phelps Actions and Unity Vigil, Thursday, March 5, 2009 at 5 PM, Albany City Hall----Members of WAW and Grannies will be there., 2009 February 28
    - Join us on March 21 on the bus to Washington DC Respond ASAP, 2009 February 28
    - Today from Noon to 2 PM, RPI Call-in Radio Show to address Phelps prot and to hear from members of the communities that he targets, 2009 March 1
    - Performance & lecture on Palinian Women - this Tues, Mar 3, 7 PM, 2009 March 2
    - Take Action: No Mention of Aid to Israel in Budget, Thank Pres. Obama, 2009 March 2
    - Please be a peace voice at the candidate forums for the 20th Congressional District, 2009 March 3
    - March Calendar of WB Events and Announcements, 2009 March 4
    - Please sign our Iraqi Refugee Project Petition! And help us collect other signatures!, 2009 March 5
    - More soldiers to Afghanistan???? Opportunity for a quick message to Tonko!, 2009 March 6
    - Why Marching on the Pentagon on March 21 is Necessary..Join Us, 2009 March 8
    - Fwd: Save Your Local Farmer's Market and Your Local Farmer - Urgent Action Re..., 2009 March 8
    - TAKE ACTION to Change US Strategy in Afghanistan!, 2009 March 10
    - Senate Vote tonight on Gaza refugees, 2009 March 10
    - Here's an Update on last night's Gaza refugee vote in the Senate. Kyl ammendment was withdrawn!, 2009 March 11
    - Plans for a documentary and petition for Congressional oversight on Afghanistan, 2009 March 11
    - Mohawk filmmaker Reaghan Tarbell, Saturday, 3/14, 7 PM, Troy, 2009 March 12
    - Reminder: Afghanistan Book Discussion Group, Mon, Mar. 23, 2009 March 12
    - Annual Rachel Corrie vigil, Monday, March 16, 5PM to 6 PM, Washington Ave. Armory, Albany, 2009 March 13
    - NEPAJAC meeting this Sunday, March 15th, 2 to 4 PM at FUUSA, 405 Washington Ave. Albany, 2009 March 13
    - Iraq War SIXTH ANNIVERSARY GATHERINGS, taking place locally, 3/16, 3/18, 3/19, 3/20, 3/21, 2009 March 15
    - "Myth America" by Cindy Sheehan: Internet booklet, Pre-order your copy ..., 2009 March 15
    - Greg Mortenson, 3 Cups of Tea author, speaking on April 13th, 2009 March 16
    - WAWaction Iraq War SIXTH ANNIVERSARY GATHERINGS, taking place locally, 3/16, 3/18, 3/19, 3/20, 3/21, 2009 March 16
    - Exciting Children's Mural Workshop! "Building a Culture of Peace: How will they know?", 2009 March 17
    - The Sanctuary - The B of Fence and more!, 2009 March 18
    - 6th Anniversary of the Iraq Invasion - Local events, 2009 March 18
    - Chatham Peace Initiative Vigil, 2009 March 18
    - Happy Nowruz, 1388. To Iranian and Kurdish friends and others who celebrate this holiday, a peaceful, joyful New Year., 2009 March 18
    - BBC: Israeli troops admit Gaza abuses, 2009 March 20
    - A Look Back at The 6th Anniversary of The Iraq Occupation, 2009 March 23
    - WAW members invited to join Code Pink at April 4th March in NYC!, 2009 March 24
    - Potluck for 4/3 at Sanctuary with Wafaa Bilal - contact Marcia if you can come, 2009 March 25
    - Local Residents attended the March to the Pentagon in DC Saturday, 3/21, and links to more pictures from several sources...., 2009 March 25
    - April 7, 2009, Albany Law School, 5:30 PM, "Waiting for Mercy", a documentary about the FBI & Yassin Aref and Mohammed Hossain, 2009 March 26
    - Kabul in Winter, 2009 March 27
    - TONIGHT ! TURN OFF YOUR LIGHTS! FOR EARTH HOUR !, 2009 March 28
    - Tell Obama: End the Afghan War Now -- Don't Escalate It! Some action suggions from Voters for Peace and Friends Committee on National Legislation, 2009 March 29
    - Reminder TODAY is the National Call in Day for the Cluster Munitions Civilian Protection Act, 2009 March 30
    - First Friday Opening - Connie Frisbee Houde's photos, 2009 March 31
    - Upstate Girls, Shoot An Iraqi, 2009 April 1
    - Celebrate Granny Peacemakers - Monday, April 27, 2009 - 7:00 PM, 2009 April 2
    - Cindy Sheehan Concludes:- Solution is HALT TO MILITARY RECRUITMENT, 2009 April 3
    - ** Urgent. Release Wall Street Arrees!, 2009 April 4
    - Tell your Senators: "Time to start talking with Iran in a real effort at diplomacy." Action requ from FCNL, 2009 April 6
    - Candlelight Vigil for Binghamton immigrants, Wednesday, April 8th at 5:30 PM, Townsend Park, Albany, 2009 April 7
    - Join the Grannies for Peace Vigil at the Tulip Fival!, 2009 April 7
    - Robert Hillary King, author, activist innocent Angola inmate, Friday, April 10, 7 PM, 2009 April 8
    - April is Sexual Assault Awareness Month! Some events, background, and contact information, 2009 April 8
    - Help Prevent an Accidental War with Iran. An action alert concerning the negotiation of an "Incidents at Sea Agreement" with Iran, 2009 April 8
    - WAW Iran Project Meeting On Monday, April 20th - meeting time CHANGED to 11 AM instead of Noon, for April only, 2009 April 12
    - Action ! Sit-In- Please come or fwd to friends in Boston area-, 2009 April 13
    - NOW Action - A National Disgrace: Stop Sexual Assault in the Military, 2009 April 14
    - A Victory For War-Stoppers " Time Magazine, 2009 April 16
    - Women"s Building Crunch and Brunch, 2009 April 16
    - Take Action: Amny International - Infamous Torture Memo Released, 2009 April 17
    - Reminder: Celebration of Granny Peacemakers - Mon, April 27, 6:30 PM, 2009 April 20
    - The perfect Mother's Day present for your favorite granny!, 2009 April 21
    - Troy Night Out w/ filmmaker Su Friedrich "From the Ground Up" plus Upstate Girls, 2009 April 22
    - REMINDER: [Albany Refugee Support] Home Across Lands - Refugee Documentary - April 29, 7pm, Page Hall, SUNYA, 2009 April 23
    - WB Brunch and Crunch Schedule of Events!, 2009 April 24
    - Reminder: Col. Ann Wright speaks Monday, May 4th at 6PM, First Church in Albany, 2009 April 29
    - WAW Showing Rick Steves Iran special at Colonie Library, Thurs May 7, 7 PM, 2009 April 30
    - Stand with Obama on Israel and Iran, 2009 April 30
    - A way you can help the Iraqi Refugee Project help refugees in our area, 2009 May 1
    - Opportunity to sign the third 'projectsalam_letter_03' petition signature, concerning prosecution of Muslims, illegal detention and torture, 2009 May 3
    - Silent Vigil, please join us Saturday, May 9, 2009, 1 PM to 2 PM, Rain or Shine! We will also be a part of a national and international effort----, 2009 May 4
    - Traditional Buddhist Flower Fival, Sunday May 10, 11am with potluck following, at Grafton Peace Pagoda, 2009 May 4
    - Fwd: Feds Threaten Cindy Sheehan, 2009 May 4
    - Invitation from MoveOn organizer, Joe Seeman: Join me at a Power Up America Organizing Meeting, 2009 May 5
    - Re: WAWaction Silent Vigil and parallel Code Pink Vigil in Washington, DC on Mother's Day, 2009 May 5
    - Kabul in Winter, May 11, 2009 May 5
    - An inspiring story about another effect of Pete Seeger's music and the power of a good folk song!, 2009 May 5
    - I will personally deliver your message to Iran, 2009 May 5
    - Two Wheels Good, Race Course w/ Bill Ayers and Bernardine Dohrn, 2009 May 6
    - Father Louis Vitale, 76 year old Peace activist, recently returned from Iran Friday, May 15, Pastoral Center, Albany NY Potluck and Talk, 2009 May 6
    - An Invitation to Attend a National Antiwar Conference, July 10-12, Pittsburgh PA, 2009 May 7
    - Save the Date--Afghanistan: Understanding the Issues, 2009 May 7
    - Reading of the Memoir Project by local authors, Monday, May 11, 2009, 7 PM Arts Center, Troy NY, 2009 May 9
    - Lyn Miller-Lachmann to discuss her new book, "gringolandia" Tuesday, May 19, at 7 PM, Albany Public Library, 2009 May 9
    - ALAEI DAY IS TUESDAY!!! Call MONDAY at 11, 2009 May 11
    - Virtual Day of Action to free AIDS activist physicians Kamiar and Arash Alaei, Imprisoned in Iran since June of 2008, 2009 May 11
    - Urgent action needed on Iran, 2009 May 12
    - Great TV coverage of the Iraqi Refugee Project, 2009 May 13
    - It's My Life - appeal to WAW list, 2009 May 13
    - GOOD NEWS!! We've Moved! The Women's Building, 2009 May 13
    - Cuba presentation, 2009 May 13
    - "It's My Life" - appeal to WAW list, 2009 May 13
    - " Stop the bloodbath" an action alert concerning Sri Lanka and its major donor and trading partner, Japan, 2009 May 14
    - Children's Memorial Day Flower Vigil, 2009 May 14
    - Another chance to hear Lyn Miller-Lachman read from her book about Pinochet's Chile, as told through the eyes of a fictional family, Sunday, May 17, 1 PM to 2:30 PM, Schenectady, 2009 May 15
    - PLEASE HELP SPREAD THE WORD! Albany vigil for Troy Davis Tuesday, 5/19, 6PM to 7PM, Townsend Park, Albany, 2009 May 16
    - Shameful Vote in the House Passes War Funding Bill, 2009 May 17
    - Albany Memorial Day Parade May 25th. Gather between 9 am and 9:30 am to walk with Veterans for Peace and other Peace Groups, 2009 May 18
    - Link to article: Disease of Permanent War, by Chris Hedges, 2009 May 19
    - EMPTY BOWLS event, at Bethlehem High School sponsored by Students for Peace and Survival, Wednesday 5/27, 6 to 8 PM, 2009 May 20
    - Live From Lock One: Tana Asili y la Bande Rebelde plu s The Ameros, 2009 May 20
    - Great speakers on Afghanistan: Sat, June 13, 6:30 PM - please come!, 2009 May 22
    - Interfaith Story Circle meeting Dances of Universal Peace, Wednesday, June 10, 7 PM to 9 PM, Hubbard Hall, Albany, 2009 May 22
    - Bishop Gibbons HS giving out military propaganda, 2009 May 26
    - An Iraq war CO begins a nation-wide walking, biking tour - starting today!, 2009 May 27
    - The Jimmy Massey Story, co-founder of Iraq Veterans Against the War, Saturday, June 6, 2009, 8 PM to 10 PM, Sanctuary for Independent Media, 2009 June 1
    - Terrific interview with Mabel Leon about her Cuba & other peace work, 2009 June 1
    - Reminder: Major WAW Afghanistan event, June 13th, 6:30 PM - please come!, 2009 June 2
    - Reminder: IVAW's Jimmy Massey plus filmmaker Joe Stillman w/ "From Mills River to Babylon", 2009 June 3
    - Donating money to the two anti-hunger charities designated by Students for Peace and Survival during "Empty Bowls", 2009 June 3
    - Some commentary on the murder of abortion provider, Dr. George Tiller, from Women's eNews, 2009 June 3
    - GRINGOLANDIA book signing on Saturday, 2009 June 4
    - FOR invites you to Iran in July for a solidarity action, 2009 June 4
    - Phyllis Bennis' Obama speech analysis, 2009 June 5
    - Physicians for a National Health Progran present " Jammin' for Single Payer!!!" Albany, Friday, June 12, 5:30 PM to 10 PM, 2009 June 6
    - Women's Building Happenings!, 2009 June 8
    - If you live in the Bethlehem School District, Hearing on a new Opt-Out Policy at Board Of Education Meeting, Wednesday, June 17th at 7 PM, 2009 June 9
    - Please Sign Letter to President Obama and Attorney General Holder about Wrongfully Prosecuted Muslims and the use of entrapment by the FBI, 2009 June 9
    - ATTEND THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY CONFERENCE, 2009 June 9
    - Connie Frisbee Houde & Madelyn Hoffman speak on Afghanistan this Saturday!, 2009 June 11
    - NEW MUSLIM COOL PBS documentary in Albany Friday June 19th, 2009 June 11
    - CALL WITHOUT DELAY - TODAY: Easy to use tool to call all undecided Reps..., 2009 June 14
    - Report on Iraqi Refugee Project delegation visit to DC, 2009 June 15
    - background on Iranian election and prots/AFFIRM IRANIAN PROT IRAN: WEAR GREEN!, 2009 June 15
    - National Campaign for Nonviolent Resistance (NCNR) Action June 25, at the Department of Justice Washington DC, 2009 June 16
    - Important film on Lyme Disease Wednesday, June 24 and Thursday, June 25, & other selected items from the BNP peace email, 2009 June 16
    - Taif completes first year at Union!, 2009 June 16
    - See Us Live in NYC This Week + On PBS Next Week, 2009 June 18
    - Teen Peace Camp July 6th to 9th in Medusa New York, 2009 June 19
    - Monday, July 13, 7 PM at Albany Public Library, "Education as a Tool for Justice and Peace in the Middle East", 2009 June 21
    - Fw: 11th Annual Interfaith Kateri Tekakwtiha Peace Conference, Friday and Saturday August 14 and August 15, Fonda New York, 2009 June 21
    - Attend the National Assembly Conference, July 10 - 12 in Pittsburgh, 2009 June 22
    - NEW MUSLIM COOL -Co produced by Kauthar Umar, my daughter, in The New York Times!, 2009 June 23
    - WB Happenings July and more, 2009 June 24
    - Attend the National Assembly Conference, July 10 - 12 in Pittsburgh, 2009 June 24
    - Work Party at the WB Saturday!, 2009 June 26
    - Iraq War Veteran & Conscientious Object Josh Steiber will speak in Delmar - Thursday, July 9, 7:00 - 8:45 pm, 2009 June 26
    - Israel Attacks Justice Boat in International Waters, confiscates aid--and kidnaps human rights workers & What You Can Do, 2009 June 30
    - National Assembly conference, July 10-12, Pittsburgh, to kick off G-20 organizing, 2009 June 30
    - "Our generations can rid the world of nuclear weapons", a call for us to send a message to President Obama [from Peace Action W], 2009 July 1
    - "I really need a favor... " Requ to watch a short video and contact your Representative to close the School of the Americas, 2009 July 1
    - Reminder: Iraq War Veteran and Conscientious Objector, Josh Steiber, Thursday July 9, 7 PM to 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library, 2009 July 1
    - IACenter.org article: http://www.iacenter.org/paline/gazashipment_petition063009/, 2009 July 2
    - "Peace-atorium" potluck, Ballston Spa, 3 PM, Sunday, July 5, 2009, 2009 July 3
    - Learning history not war! Fwd: Finished Site, 2009 July 5
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation provides an easy way to write to your Representative about an exit strategy from Afghanistan, 2009 July 7